Tufts College Treasurer's Report UP216
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts College Treasurer's Report
1885 -- 1967
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Trustees of Tufts College
UP216
0.25 Linear Feet
9 Volumes
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains the published version of the Tufts College Treasurer's report. Earlier reports, 1875-1884, are contained in the Board of Trustees files UA003.
Related Materials
UA003, Office of the Board of Trustees records, DCA
Biographical / Historical
In 1851, a Board of Trustees was nominated by the subscribers to replace the temporary Board created at the 1847 Educational Convention of the Universalist Church. The new Board selected a site and drew up the governing rules for the new College.
- Tufts College Treasurer's Report, 1885 -- 1967; 1875 -- 1954; UP216.001; 0.25 Linear Feet; 9 Volumes
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains the published version of the Tufts College Treasurer's report.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Treasurer's Report, 1885; UP216.001.001.00001 (Box Volume 1)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1886; UP216.001.001.00002 (Box Volume 1)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1887; UP216.001.001.00003 (Box Volume 1)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1888; UP216.001.001.00004 (Box Volume 1)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1889; UP216.001.001.00005 (Box Volume 1)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1890; UP216.001.001.00006 (Box Volume 1)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1891; UP216.001.001.00007 (Box Volume 1)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1892; UP216.001.001.00008 (Box Volume 1)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1893; UP216.001.001.00009 (Box Volume 1)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1894; UP216.001.001.00010 (Box Volume 1)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1895; UP216.001.001.00011 (Box Volume 1)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1896; UP216.001.001.00012 (Box Volume 1)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1897; UP216.001.001.00013 (Box Volume 1)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1898; UP216.001.001.00014 (Box Volume 1)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1899; UP216.001.001.00015 (Box Volume 1)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1900; UP216.001.002.00001 (Box Volume 2)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1901; UP216.001.002.00002 (Box Volume 2)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1902; UP216.001.002.00003 (Box Volume 2)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1903; UP216.001.002.00004 (Box Volume 2)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1904; UP216.001.002.00005 (Box Volume 2)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1905; UP216.001.002.00006 (Box Volume 2)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1906; UP216.001.002.00007 (Box Volume 2)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1907; UP216.001.002.00008 (Box Volume 2)
  - Special Report of Treasurer, 1904 -- 1906; UP216.001.002.00009 (Box Volume 2)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1908; UP216.001.003.00001 (Box Volume 3)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1909; UP216.001.003.00002 (Box Volume 3)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1910; UP216.001.003.00003 (Box Volume 3)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1911; UP216.001.003.00004 (Box Volume 3)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1912; UP216.001.003.00005 (Box Volume 3)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1913; UP216.001.003.00006 (Box Volume 3)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1914; UP216.001.003.00007 (Box Volume 3)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1915; UP216.001.004.00001 (Box Volume 4)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1916; UP216.001.004.00002 (Box Volume 4)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1917; UP216.001.004.00003 (Box Volume 4)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1918; UP216.001.004.00004 (Box Volume 4)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1919; UP216.001.004.00005 (Box Volume 4)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1920; UP216.001.004.00006 (Box Volume 4)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1921; UP216.001.004.00007 (Box Volume 4)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1922; UP216.001.004.00008 (Box Volume 4)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1923; UP216.001.005.00001 (Box data_value_missing_069a92dd84b3c9ec79595ec229d1299d)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1924; UP216.001.005.00002 (Box data_value_missing_069a92dd84b3c9ec79595ec229d1299d)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1925; UP216.001.005.00003 (Box data_value_missing_069a92dd84b3c9ec79595ec229d1299d)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1926; UP216.001.005.00004 (Box data_value_missing_069a92dd84b3c9ec79595ec229d1299d)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1927; UP216.001.005.00005 (Box data_value_missing_069a92dd84b3c9ec79595ec229d1299d)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1928; UP216.001.005.00006 (Box data_value_missing_069a92dd84b3c9ec79595ec229d1299d)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1929; UP216.001.005.00007 (Box data_value_missing_069a92dd84b3c9ec79595ec229d1299d)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1930; UP216.001.006.00001 (Box data_value_missing_069a92dd84b3c9ec79595ec229d1299d)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1931; UP216.001.006.00002 (Box data_value_missing_069a92dd84b3c9ec79595ec229d1299d)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1932; UP216.001.006.00003 (Box data_value_missing_069a92dd84b3c9ec79595ec229d1299d)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1933; UP216.001.006.00004 (Box data_value_missing_069a92dd84b3c9ec79595ec229d1299d)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1934; UP216.001.006.00005 (Box data_value_missing_069a92dd84b3c9ec79595ec229d1299d)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1935; UP216.001.006.00006 (Box data_value_missing_069a92dd84b3c9ec79595ec229d1299d)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1936; UP216.001.006.00007 (Box data_value_missing_069a92dd84b3c9ec79595ec229d1299d)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1937; UP216.001.006.00008 (Box data_value_missing_069a92dd84b3c9ec79595ec229d1299d)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1938; UP216.001.006.00009 (Box data_value_missing_8c5a8b74713e329669647c0df56fac27)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1939; UP216.001.006.00010 (Box data_value_missing_8c5a8b74713e329669647c0df56fac27)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1940; UP216.001.007.00001 (Box Volume 7)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1941; UP216.001.007.00002 (Box Volume 7)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1942; UP216.001.007.00003 (Box data_value_missing_8c5a8b74713e329669647c0df56fac27)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1943; UP216.001.007.00004 (Box data_value_missing_8c5a8b74713e329669647c0df56fac27)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1944; UP216.001.007.00005 (Box data_value_missing_8c5a8b74713e329669647c0df56fac27)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1945; UP216.001.007.00006 (Box data_value_missing_8c5a8b74713e329669647c0df56fac27)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1946; UP216.001.008.00001 (Box Volume 8)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1947; UP216.001.008.00002 (Box Volume 8)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1948; UP216.001.008.00003 (Box Volume 8)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1949; UP216.001.008.00004 (Box Volume 8)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1950; UP216.001.008.00005 (Box Volume 8)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1951; UP216.001.009.00001 (Box Volume 9)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1952; UP216.001.009.00002 (Box Volume 9)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1953; UP216.001.009.00003 (Box Volume 9)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1954; UP216.001.009.00004 (Box Volume 9)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1955; UP216.001.010.00001 (Box 10)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1958; UP216.001.010.00002 (Box 10)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1967; UP216.001.010.00003 (Box 10)